<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Dimitris Glezos' old personal site - Fedora</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://127.0.0.1:8000/weblog/feeds/tag/fedora.atom" rel="self"></link><id>https://dimitris.glezos.com/</id><updated>2009-07-15T00:00:00+03:00</updated><entry><title>OpenOffice and Latex equation syntax</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2009/07/15/openoffice-and-latex-equation-syntax/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2009-07-15T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2009-07-15T00:00:00+03:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2009-07-15:/weblog/2009/07/15/openoffice-and-latex-equation-syntax/</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On Fedora: &lt;code&gt;sudo yum -y install openoffice.org-ooolatex&lt;/code&gt;. Plain. Effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category><category term="Mini-post"></category></entry><entry><title>Fedora Weekly Webcomic EOL’ed</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2009/05/23/fedora-weekly-webcomic-eoled/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2009-05-23T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2009-05-23T00:00:00+03:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2009-05-23:/weblog/2009/05/23/fedora-weekly-webcomic-eoled/</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh dear. The awesome Fedora Webcomic is &lt;a href="http://nicubunu.blogspot.com/2009/05/fedora-weekly-webcomic-end.html"&gt;being EOL’ed&lt;/a&gt;. I’ll miss the Greek Ubuntu team complaining to me: “Aren’t there any other distros to make fun of?” =)&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category><category term="Mini-post"></category></entry><entry><title>Notes from Amsterdam</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2009/03/31/notes-from-amsterdam/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2009-03-31T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2009-03-31T00:00:00+03:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2009-03-31:/weblog/2009/03/31/notes-from-amsterdam/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/51035655291@N01/2458382137/" title="Paula - Teasers"&gt;&lt;img alt="Paula - Teasers" src="http://farm3.static.flickr.com/2326/2458382137_db51a254d0_m.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
(&lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.0/" title="Published under a Creative Commons licence"&gt;cc&lt;/a&gt;) by &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/51035655291@N01/2458382137/" title="liber"&gt;liber&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feeling like the guy with the best host’s house in the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went for a walk at the local Saturday market. We bought a few stuff to cook some nice dishes during the week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Saturday afternoon the city felt more like Edinburgh than Amsterdam. The …&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/51035655291@N01/2458382137/" title="Paula - Teasers"&gt;&lt;img alt="Paula - Teasers" src="http://farm3.static.flickr.com/2326/2458382137_db51a254d0_m.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
(&lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.0/" title="Published under a Creative Commons licence"&gt;cc&lt;/a&gt;) by &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/51035655291@N01/2458382137/" title="liber"&gt;liber&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feeling like the guy with the best host’s house in the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Went for a walk at the local Saturday market. We bought a few stuff to cook some nice dishes during the week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Saturday afternoon the city felt more like Edinburgh than Amsterdam. The World Cup took place and the city was full of Scottish people drinking and singing in the street. The city center was so alive from all the joy — a great Saturday night. The Dutch &lt;em&gt;set them crying back across the English channel&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://spevack.livejournal.com/"&gt;™&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saturday night in Amsterdam, we couldn’t not go for a walk through the Red Light District. The atmosphere in that part of the city was amazing, felt like London’s Soho and other districts where primitive feelings flourish. Upon returning home I was thinking how interesting it is that there are places in big cities in the world where restrictions are lowered and freedom is given another perspective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very close to where we’re staying was the place where &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anne_Frank"&gt;Anne Frank&lt;/a&gt; wrote her diaries. It’s a bit stupid, but it makes me feel a bit strange inside. Wakes up a desire of me to stop whining and improve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’ve said so many times “Thanks! I’ll buy you a beer next time we meet!” to Max Spevack. Now that I am in Amsterdam, I’ll need to get him wasted to repay those back. Instead, I’ve decided to do some cooking for him and Diego when I’m having a break from the Transifex stuff I’m doing here. The menu so far included strong Spaghetti aglio e olio, with a note of rocket and gin, Tagliatelle carbonara with chorizo sausage and paprica, and roast chicken with rosemary and melted cheese for today.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/35008852@N00/110034985/" title="pra variar um pouco"&gt;&lt;img alt="pra variar um pouco" src="http://farm1.static.flickr.com/41/110034985_488f0d9ab7.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
(&lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/2.0/" title="Published under a Creative Commons licence"&gt;cc&lt;/a&gt;) by &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/35008852@N00/110034985/" title="Vitorio Benedetti"&gt;Vitorio Benedetti&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category><category term="Personal"></category></entry><entry><title>Amsterdam, baby!</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2009/03/28/amsterdam-baby/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2009-03-28T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2009-03-28T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2009-03-28:/weblog/2009/03/28/amsterdam-baby/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have been looking forward to this trip for quite a while. My travel has been reduced lately, as I’m preoccupied with all the great stuff happening at the Indiplex. Long hours of hacking and designing, planning and talking with clients — not much time to think and interrupt the …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have been looking forward to this trip for quite a while. My travel has been reduced lately, as I’m preoccupied with all the great stuff happening at the Indiplex. Long hours of hacking and designing, planning and talking with clients — not much time to think and interrupt the spree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But coming to Amsterdam for a week-long hackfest/brainstorm-fest with Max was just an ingenious idea to pass. The flattering comments about Max’s hospitality, house and Amsterdam itself made me much excited about the idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A consequence of working in a dynamic startup at which you’re having the time of your life, is that your sleep hours get reduced. At some points, they get reduced &lt;em&gt;a lot&lt;/em&gt;. While [releasing with the sunrise][1] is indeed a great feeling, a man needs to get a proper sleep every a few days. I could use some rest at this moment, so being in Amsterdam makes it the best excuse to just say “I’ll try to get some rest in the weekend”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And this is exactly what I’ll do. No coding for this weekend. I swear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/12836528@N00/2577006675/" title="Reflections"&gt;&lt;img alt="Reflections" src="http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3057/2577006675_b5dd38dca6.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
(&lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/2.0/" title="Published under a Creative Commons licence"&gt;cc&lt;/a&gt;) by &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/12836528@N00/2577006675/" title="kevindooley"&gt;kevindooley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category><category term="Tech/web"></category></entry><entry><title>Fedora L10n Project Advancement Study</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2009/03/08/flp-advancement-study/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2009-03-08T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2009-03-08T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2009-03-08:/weblog/2009/03/08/flp-advancement-study/</id><summary type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There are three kinds of lies: lies, damned lies, and statistics.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Twain, originally by Benjamin Disraeli&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seeing some nifty statistics from the Fedora Ambassadors group, I decided to jot down some statistics for the Localization group too. Once in a while, it helps taking a step back, and be …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There are three kinds of lies: lies, damned lies, and statistics.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Twain, originally by Benjamin Disraeli&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seeing some nifty statistics from the Fedora Ambassadors group, I decided to jot down some statistics for the Localization group too. Once in a while, it helps taking a step back, and be honest, judgemental and stern with ourselves, before finally concluding what an awesome job we did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dear reader is encouraged, with Mark Twain’s words in mind, to go on and read the following ultra-deceptive lies about FLP. The Sirens disguised as charts ruthlessly suggest and persuasively imply that the FLP, just like the Ambassadors group, is indeed growing and improving. It has been reported that the text has even created impossible feelings like, for example, that the grass is not always greener on the other side of the fence. Or that the circle has only one side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On to the data now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(In some of the following graphs you’ll notice the absence of some data between last February and today. Feel free to blame my today’s lazyness and stiffness from yesterday’s rock climbing.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="community"&gt;Community&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the past 2 years we’ve changed a lot of things on how the L10n project is structured, how the language teams are organized, and how the actual work is being done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On March 2007, the group ‘cvsl10n’ was created on the Fedora Account System. We used this group to identify translators and give them access to all projects hosted on the Fedora CVS server. Since then the Fedora Account System group has evolved and became the ID of a “Fedora Translator”. The following chart shows how the number of the Fedora Translators grew the past years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="cvsl10n" src="/weblog/wp-content/uploads/2009/03/cvsl10n.jpg" title="cvsl10n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Approximately 20 new translators join the group each month on a steady rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On communication, fedora-trans-list is the main channel of the FLP (together with #fedora-l10n of course). The following graph shows the volume of emails sent to the list for the past four years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="trans-list" src="/weblog/wp-content/uploads/2009/03/trans-list.jpg" title="trans-list"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This graph reflects the “bandwidth” increase in the FLP’s main communication channel. Compared to 2005, the list’s content for 2006 grew by 200%, and each consecutive year saw a further increase of 70%. More issues get discussed and resolved, more people participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="uptake"&gt;Uptake&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the term “project coverage” and “language coverage” we refer to the number of the resources (software, documentation, websites) we are translating, and the number of languages we are translating these resources to. High project coverage means more translated interfaces, and high language coverage means more Fedora users happy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the best translatable resources Fedora builds are the release notes. I like looking at their coverage when I talk about the health of the FLP, since they are a tough resource to translate, both because of its size and its importance for every Fedora release. Here’s a graph showing in how many languages we shipped it since day 1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="langs" src="/weblog/wp-content/uploads/2009/03/langs.jpg" title="langs"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fedora is upstream for a number of projects. The project coverage measures how many projects we can translate. Increasing this metric was one of the reasons we migrated from elvis to the open Fedora Infrastructure: to allow more projects to be translated. One and a half year later, our infrastructure has improved, the community has grown, and more and more projects request translations. The following chart shows the number of projects that were available for translation on elvis and today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="projects" src="/weblog/wp-content/uploads/2009/03/projects.jpg" title="projects"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, the following chart shows the number of commits which happened through Transifex in the past months. In total, 5400 commits took place in the past 15 months, averaging 360 commits per month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="tx-commits" src="/weblog/wp-content/uploads/2009/03/tx-commits1.jpg" title="tx-commits"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The string freeze periods where translators push their contributions can be seen as the ups in the chart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="l10n-engineering"&gt;L10n engineering&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main FLP tools live in cvs.fedoraproject.org (for now [hg soon], muahaha), ‘L10N’ repo. Files needed by the FLP to work properly are maintained there, such as the translation interface and the &lt;code&gt;owners.list&lt;/code&gt; file that syncs with Bugzilla to have components created.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By February 2009, around 3000 commits have landed on cvs/L10n measuring around 125 commits per month, or 4 per day. It’s worth noting that this repository receives a lot of love by our community members (thumbs-up to &lt;a href="http://fedoraproject.org/wiki/PiotrDr%C4%85g"&gt;Piotr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://diegobz.net/"&gt;Diego&lt;/a&gt;). These guys have been tirelessly maintaining the tools and keeping them in shape to serve our translation community as best as possible. The following chart helps illustrate the involvement of the volunteer community (non Red Hat employees) in the Fedora Localization toolchain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="resources" src="/weblog/wp-content/uploads/2009/03/resources.gif" title="resources"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extremely happy to see so much community involvement in the admin side of FLP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$me happy, listening to “Side” by Travis.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category></entry><entry><title>Fedora Board decisions in the open</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2009/01/22/fedora-board-decisions-in-the-open/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2009-01-22T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2009-01-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2009-01-22:/weblog/2009/01/22/fedora-board-decisions-in-the-open/</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’m so glad folks on the Fedora Board are &lt;a href="https://fedoraproject.org/wiki/Board/Meetings/2009-01-20"&gt;insisting&lt;/a&gt; on taking discussions that could be discussed in the open to our public advisory board list.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category><category term="Mini-post"></category><category term="Thoughts"></category></entry><entry><title>A seat on the Fedora Board</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2009/01/10/a-seat-on-the-fedora-board/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2009-01-10T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2009-01-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2009-01-10:/weblog/2009/01/10/a-seat-on-the-fedora-board/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Either due to ignorance or simply blunt encouragement for my evil plans for &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2BRXmgcBHBM"&gt;World Domination&lt;/a&gt; ™ (wicked music played in the background), I was appointed by Red Hat to take &lt;a href="https://www.redhat.com/archives/fedora-announce-list/2009-January/msg00007.html"&gt;a seat on the Fedora Board&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2BRXmgcBHBM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll start off by saying a big ‘Thank you’ to all who supported my …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Either due to ignorance or simply blunt encouragement for my evil plans for &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2BRXmgcBHBM"&gt;World Domination&lt;/a&gt; ™ (wicked music played in the background), I was appointed by Red Hat to take &lt;a href="https://www.redhat.com/archives/fedora-announce-list/2009-January/msg00007.html"&gt;a seat on the Fedora Board&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2BRXmgcBHBM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll start off by saying a big ‘Thank you’ to all who supported my candidacy and this decision. Fedora has evolved into one of the most influential and vibrant Linux distributions today and it’s a great honour to serve on its &lt;a href="https://fedoraproject.org/wiki/Board"&gt;Board&lt;/a&gt; and represent the community on the issues the Board is accountable for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I joined Fedora as a contributor much later than a lot of other folks. I still remember the enthusiasm when my Fedora account was approved. Since then I got a lot of similar enthusiasms: first patch accepted, first influencial changeset accepted, email from the Leader, first conference… they’re so many. Now I’m yet again thrilled for having an opportunity to experience new things and serve the community in a different way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first thing on my agenda is take some time and grasp the new responsibilities and the areas I’d like to be accountable for. I’ve written quite a few big goals on &lt;a href="https://fedoraproject.org/wiki/Board/Elections/Nominations#Dimitris_Glezos_.28glezos.29"&gt;my mission statement&lt;/a&gt; and I’d like to start talking with people right away about them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is one of the reasons I just booked myself a ticket to &lt;a href="http://fosdem.org/2009/"&gt;FOSDEM&lt;/a&gt;. I’ll mostly hang around the Fedora booth and the Python devroom, in case you’d like to find me and have some more TODOs added on my agenda. Or just fire up your email client and get in contact with any issues you’d like to discuss as part of my new role.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Off for some satanic thoughts now with my hot chocolate before going to bed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category><category term="Personal"></category><category term="Thoughts"></category><category term="Transifex"></category></entry><entry><title>Results of Fedora Board Elections</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2008/12/21/fbe-10-results/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2008-12-21T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2008-12-21T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2008-12-21:/weblog/2008/12/21/fbe-10-results/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Came out 3rd on the recent &lt;a href="https://www.redhat.com/archives/fedora-announce-list/2008-December/msg00019.html"&gt;Elections for the Fedora Board&lt;/a&gt;. I’m &lt;em&gt;extremely&lt;/em&gt; happy with the result, as Bill and Matt are two fantastic guys who have tons to offer. I’m also humbled from the number of votes I received — I’ll take it as a sign to …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Came out 3rd on the recent &lt;a href="https://www.redhat.com/archives/fedora-announce-list/2008-December/msg00019.html"&gt;Elections for the Fedora Board&lt;/a&gt;. I’m &lt;em&gt;extremely&lt;/em&gt; happy with the result, as Bill and Matt are two fantastic guys who have tons to offer. I’m also humbled from the number of votes I received — I’ll take it as a sign to keep working hard. Now, go eat some turkey and let’s get our butts back to work and ship yet another great release.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category><category term="Mini-post"></category></entry><entry><title>Υποψηφιότητα Αθήνας για Ευρω-FUDCon 2009</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2008/12/18/%CF%85%CF%80%CE%BF%CF%88%CE%B7%CF%86%CE%B9%CF%8C%CF%84%CE%B7%CF%84%CE%B1-%CE%B1%CE%B8%CE%AE%CE%BD%CE%B1%CF%82-%CE%B3%CE%B9%CE%B1-%CE%B5%CF%85%CF%81%CF%89-fudcon-2009/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2008-12-18T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2008-12-18T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2008-12-18:/weblog/2008/12/18/υποψηφιότητα-αθήνας-για-ευρω-fudcon-2009/</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Μόλις ανέβασα μερικές πληροφορίες για την υποψηφιότητα της Αθήνας για το &lt;a href="https://fedoraproject.org/wiki/FUDCon/FUDConEMEA2009#Athens"&gt;FUDCon EMEA 2009&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category><category term="Mini-post"></category></entry><entry><title>Fedora Board voting live</title><link href="https://dimitris.glezos.com/weblog/2008/12/10/fedora-board-voting-live/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2008-12-10T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2008-12-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Dimitris Glezos</name></author><id>tag:dimitris.glezos.com,2008-12-10:/weblog/2008/12/10/fedora-board-voting-live/</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A few days now we’ve got the &lt;a href="https://admin.fedoraproject.org/voting/about/boardf11"&gt;Fedora Board Elections&lt;/a&gt; live. Check out the awesome group of candidates we have and cast your vote.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="random"></category><category term="Fedora"></category><category term="Mini-post"></category></entry></feed>